Now we're married, aren't we,
Sakamoto-san?
Yes, Himiko.
In the world of BTOOOM!.
Here, all we have are hearts that
believe in each other's humanity.
This may be a pure true love.
Still...
I want to meet you.
Let's not.
I like it this way.
I want to keep dreaming this way.
I like you this way.
Himiko...
If they're farther away in my next scan,
we won't have to fight.
Damn it.
What the hell?
He attacked me with a knife, not a BIM?
Don't move!
Why did you attack me?
Don't you think trying to
kill each other is stupid?!
Stop this, and work with us.
We'll escape together.
How?
Well...
No plan, huh?
You can't beat a BIM with a knife!
First persuasion, then threats?
I hate selfish kids like you
more than anything.
Say what you like.
I'm leaving.
If you try to follow me...
That's what I just saw...
They're working together?
An explosion!
That's where Sakamoto-han went, isn't it?
Is he okay?
He has three types of BIMs...
For all that talk, you're a murderer, too!
There isn't any point in wasting BIMs on him.
Miyamoto-san, stab him with your knife.
If you want, I can—
Damn it!
What did you do?
W-Wait!
The stun gun's power is dropping.
Crap!
That stupid kid...
Miyamoto-san, go after him...
I was planning to let him go.
This is what he said to me:
"Work with us."
Virtual Bride
He has friends.
S-Sakamoto-han!
You're late...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But my BIMs were taken.
You didn't let them follow you, did you?
It's all right.
I took the longest way back I could find.
And they weren't using their radar.
They must have lost track of me by now.
Radar?
No!
Footprints or other traces like that!
No, I can't stay here...
I'm leaving.
Return my stuff.
Wait.
There's only one trunk.
Then give it to me.
Listen...
What?
Don't move.
H-How did you find us?
I'm a former mercenary.
Tracking someone in the
jungle is simple for me.
We meet again, girl.
When I saw his stun gun, I realized...
If I followed him, we might meet again.
Are those the BIMs and the
food you took from me?
I'm taking them back.
Come to think of it, wasn't that
fat-ass Akechi with you?
You killed him, didn't you?
Do you have his chip?
I-It wasn't me!
It's not my fault!
I don't know where his chip is.
I don't have it!
That's fine.
I'll strip off your clothes, and search for it.
Stop it!
Leave us alone...
Get out of here!
You still don't understand?
This island is hell.
You live or you die.
It's impossible to escape on your own.
The only way out is to kill
others and take the chips.
Don't you want to get eight
chips and leave this place?
If you ask me, the people playing the game
are the sane ones.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
No matter what's going on,
that doesn't give you a reason to kill!
This is a game someone made.
A game this size must have
balancing issues somewhere.
I worked as a debugger for Tyrannos Japan,
the guys who are probably running this.
So somehow, I can tell!
This game isn't complete.
It's still being developed.
There's a blind spot somewhere.
I know it!
Your plan is nothing but a
child's foolish optimism.
I'm not interested.
Die.
It'll be a pain getting that chip...
Right, girl?
Himiko...
Himiko.
H-Himiko...
Ouch.
I fell from up there?
G-Guys!
Taira-san?
S-Sakamoto-han...
We need to stop the blood.
The trunk...
And the BIMs!
He took them?
Where's the girl?
Did he take her?
No...
It's my fault.
It's all my fault...
BTOOOM!?
A type theta cosplay?
Himiko...
That's her name?
No way... Then she's...
Himiko?
I have to go.
I have to save her.
Himiko...
No! Don't go!
Please don't go...
I can't handle any more waiting...
We need clean towels and water for you.
I'll be back soon.
I promise.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
This time, it's over...
If you leave me here, I...
I won't be able to stay sane.
Please... Stay here!
Sa...
Sakamoto!
That's good stuff...
Stop!
I feel so much better.
That's my food!
You bitch,
that was mine to begin with.
Just hurry up and kill me.
I won't fight back...
In exchange,
let me die pure...
Did you think that's why I brought you here?
There are better forms of
entertainment on a battlefield.
Torturing the enemy...
Lynching.
Like peeling the skin off an apple.
Tear off all the skin,
and see how long they survive.
You can stay pure,
just the way you want...
No!
What?
That was a radar, wasn't it?
That old guy with the Kansai accent?
Or another player?
Don't you dare!
They each fired their radar twice.
Do you think it's some kind of signal?
Which means it's probably...
That kid survived.
The squall stopped.
He'll be here soon.
You head to the front hall.
I'll go around from the left.
We took all his BIMs.
He's unarmed, so don't screw up.
Leave it to me.
Your BIMs have a ten-second
delay before they explode.
Set them to three, so you don't mess up.
Right!
Okay...
He's heading toward Natsume.
The fool.
I can tell exactly where you are.
Natsume, did you get him?
He's getting closer.
Did Natsume miss?
No, he didn't.
If there isn't another explosion,
did he get Natsume?
He's heading straight for me.
So he'll be coming through here.
I'll take him in one strike.
Do you think I can't hear you?
You're mine!
Where is he?
What happened?
I s-saw him, so I attacked.
But he disappeared completely.
Is it possible to blow someone up so
completely there's nothing left?
Of course not, fool.
Look harder!
I'm certain she was around here.
That was close...
That was a military-style trap.
But I dodged it.
And I got a valuable BIM.
A BIM that's been disabled
becomes the property of
whoever disarmed it.
I proved that with her BIM.
Maybe I can create a miracle with this.
I came to save you, Himiko.
H-How did you know that name?
Sorry, I saw your phone wallpaper.
You played BTOOOM! as "Himiko," didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
It isn't my real name.
My name is Sakamoto.
Have you ever heard it?
It's possible we've played together a lot.
I know it.
If you mean the world-ranked player.
You were famous among my friends.
But all I know is the name.
I've never played with him.
It wasn't you?
I don't play that much.
That's true.
That game sold three million copies.
Of course there would be
users sharing the same name.
But I got the courage to come this far
because I thought it was Himiko.
So from now on,
I'll just have to believe in my heart.
Even if it's not your real name,
can I call you Himiko?
I guess I don't mind.
Thanks.
That bastard's with the girl.
He never showed up on the radar!
He made it through the
trap and into the room?
Christ... The radar, the BIMs...
I knew this was the only
thing I could trust.
There are only two ways
down from that room.
You go this way.
I'll get the side.
Don't screw it up this time.
Right!
Yahoo!
Penal Code Section 361
Article 1, self-defense!
Necessary actions taken in
defense of a pressing
and illegal threat are not punishable by law!
Self-defense! Self-defense!
I found you!
Die, die, die!
Unarmed fool!
I can't die in this crazy world...
I am an elite lawyer!
Fool!
That's a dead end...
Not bad, kid.
I'm impressed.
But I've got the girl.
Come on out.
I'll give you a chance.
An unarmed fight.
It's not a bad deal, is it?
Now, come on out.
If I can get that...
Your pouch had three BIM types.
You should have at least two chips.
This girl killed that Akechi fat-ass,
so she has one, too.
I said I don't have it—
You're still playing dumb?
That's fine...
You should have three between you.
Once I kill you, I can take my time looking.
Natsume, the guy with the Kansai accent,
and the one I killed before make eight total.
That's all I need.
So come on out!
If you beat me, you can get all eight, too.
Now.
The knife's the first thing
most people go for!
Damn it!
I won't let you die easily.
I said to fight barehanded.
But you ignored me and went for the knife.
That's against the rules...
Is this the end of my life?
Life didn't work out the way I wanted.
I thought it would somehow,
but it never did.
A life wasted on games.
If I could have at least
met the real Himiko...
What are you doing?
You bitch...
Hurry, run!
What did you...
What?
Run! This way!
She flipped the switch?
The gas is coming!
Where's the exit?
A dead end?
No way...
What are you going to do?
Wow.
Come on!
Gotcha.
Just a little more...
What?
I-I'll show you hell.
The real hell that I saw on the battlefield.
He's good.
But...
A timer?
Why would he?
It'll be ten seconds until it explodes.
I've got plenty of time.
I'll make it mine and toss it back...
Set them to three, so you don't mess up.
He took Natsume's...
S-Sorry.
Wow!
Wonderful.
It's like a movie.
Sakamoto-kun defeated Miyamoto
Masashi, who was favored to win!
What do you think, everyone?
In the third round, the game
balance has really improved!
After Himiko and I just barely
fended off the enemy players,
a new threat approaches.
A white ghost that Himiko
says she saw in the darkness.
Does it mean there's a new enemy?
Episode 8: White Ghost
Or is it...